# NICK MOIGNARD

## PROFILE

I am a self-taught React on Rails developer based in Melbourne. I have proven experience with both front and back end development, and a strong understanding of SQL databases, Agile Scrums, machine learning, SEO analysis, web scraping bots, Docker and Dev Ops.

## CONTACT

**2** +61 434 232 906

⊠ nicklmoignard@gmail.com

➤ Victoria Grove, Hawthorn Victoria 3122

## EXPERIENCE

#### LEAD DEVELOPER

## Hey Influencers | April 2019 - Present

- Updating and debugging dependency related errors across Rails, React, and ReactNative Applications.
- Solving security vulnerabilities presented by legacy third party software.
- Performing cost analysis of third party developer kits, resulting in \$1400 saved monthly through internal rebuilds and modernisation with open source alternatives.
- Converting ES5 Javascript to ES6.

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

## Cool Shirtz | April 2018 - April 2019

- Developing Python scripts to shape data sets which conform with shipping providers.
- Improving user experience by implementing engaging front end features.
- Analysing performance through SEO, paid Facebook advertisements and site traffic.
- Creating a private Shopify embedded application.
- Customising a third party Shopify theme.

## EDUCATION

#### UNIVERSITY OF MELBOURNE

# Bachelor of Biomedicine | 2015 - 2017 (Unfin)

- Major in Biomedical Engineering
- Melbourne University Accelerator Program: European Innovation Academy Sponsorship

#### SWINBURNE UNIVERSITY

# Bachelor of Science | 2014 - 2015 (Unfin)

- Major in Chemistry
- Finalist 2014 Swinburne Entrepreneurship Program

# SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails
- PostgreSQL
- React.js
- Python
- Entrepreneurship

# INTERESTS

- Machine learning
- Automation
- Cyber security
- Social network manipulation
- Videography